Hayato-kun...
Have we pinpointed
Kisaragi Hayato's current location?
We have.
We've requested assistance
from any Slayers close by.
He'll just have to hold it off
until reinforcements arrive.
You should be able to get through this...
No, I know you can,
Kisaragi Hayato.
The Diva's  Love Song
I didn't realize I'd lose so much mobility
and power without my variable suit.
Hayato-kun, you focus on attacking!
Hundred On!
Sakura!
I might not be able to attack,
but I can defend!
Hayato-kun!
Thank you. You're a big help.
I'm going to end this.
Shatter!
Yay! That's my hubby!
I've fallen in love with you all over again!
D-Dummy, get off of me.
People are going to get the wrong idea.
I wouldn't mind.
Are you serious?
That's Kirishima Sakura, right?
I-I can't believe it.
No way.
A Savage.
Sakura!
Fritz!
I'm here, too!
Hayato, I'm here to help... you.
Thanks, Emile. You saved us.
Emile?
This is what you get for just
leaving me there like that.
Reitia!
I know!
I couldn't get all the way to the core!
I'll finish it off, then!
It's regenerating?
It's a regenerater!
Regenerater?
We learned about them in class, right?
It's a Savage with the ability
to heal itself.
We just need to get its core...
I'm going to cut off its arms again...
Fritz and Reitia, can you cover me?
No problem.
Hayato, you finish it off.
Sure. But...
I'm fine.
You do what you need to do.
Sakura...
Got it.
Hayato, did something happen
with Kirishima-san?
O-Of course not.
I don't believe you.
Can you two save your
lovers' quarrel for later?
Let's go!
Yeah!
Hayato!
How can it regenerate its arms that fast?!
Stop it!
It reacted to her voice?
Here we go!
Hayato-kun!
Who's this guy?
Hayato-kun! Hayato-kun!
That girl's voice
was able to get through to the Savage?
Interesting.
Hayato-kun, are you okay?
Trace On.
Not happening.
Limit out.
Who are these guys?
If he gets that much of its juices on himself...
Hey! Stop it!
You're going to get infected and go crazy!
I told you to stop!
Reitia!
Don't get in Nesat's way!
How dare you!
Too slow!
Fritz!
You've done it now!
Emile!
Not on my watch!
Oh? You managed to stop my Orthrus Liberio?
Are these guys...
During the Savage attack last month,
a variable stone was stolen from
the concert venue amid all that chaos.
Hayato-kun!
Stay away!
Little Garden's lapdog is
trying to act like a prince, huh?
That puny sword isn't going to do
anything against my Duo Valga!
You're doing pretty well
without your variable suit.
However, this is the end.
He's a Variant?
Get crushed!
Hayato!
Keep your eyes on your opponent!
The form of his Hundred changed.
Looks like he has special abilities,
in line with Nee-chan.
What are you after?!
Looks like our work here is done.
Work?
Those are Savage cores...
Krovanh, they're getting closer.
How about we bounce, then, Nee-chan?
I'm sure Vitaly will be happy
if we bring this many cores back.
Vitaly...
Looks like you get to live another day.
Want to chase after them?
No...
We can't do anything about them right now.
Not in this state, no.
There's the rescue squad.
You probably ran into poachers,
Hunters.
Hunters?
Slayers who are part of illegal organizations
that don't necessarily follow the law.
The corpse of the remaining single unknown
Savage was found in the wastelands.
The core was removed, as well.
They did that too, huh?
Most likely.
But why the cores?
Because the molecular structure of Savage cores
is almost the same as a variable stone.
Wait!
You can't tell normal students that!
There's no point in hiding it from them.
Or are you trying to say that kids
don't need to know about that,
much like your brother and father do?
Does that mean a Savage core can be
reconfigured to function as a Hundred?
That's right.
In practice, it means that a core has
the same worth as a variable stone.
Monetarily, as well.
It could also change
the power balance of a country.
Anyway, this conversation
is to be considered top-secret.
I'm just glad you're all safe.
Actually, why did you guys come to help?
After I got the emergency call,
I contacted those two.
I knew they were close by.
About that...
Fritz Glanz, Reitia Saintemilion...
I cannot permit anyone to go
into battle without approval first.
Emile Crossfode.
It was possible that your actions could have
led the two of them to their deaths.
I want you to think about what you did.
Right...
However, I believe you demonstrated
exemplary traits in an emergency situation.
I will consider your entry into Selections.
We did it.
Yeah.
I'm sorry about today.
I know we were on a date...
No, it's not like it was your fault.
The clothes I got are all ruined, too.
We can just get new ones.
Could you pick them out for me again?
Sure!
Hey, stop. This is bad.
I don't wanna.
What are you going to do if someone sees us?
It's fine.
No, it isn't.
Tomorrow's the big day.
Yeah.
I finally get to sing in this special place
for my mother and me.
Yeah, that was always a dream of yours.
Sing for your mom.
No, Nii-san!
Watch closely. This is how you do it!
Right...
Do a good job.
You're Sakura's bodyguard, Nii-san.
Don't be an embarrassment
while cheering for her.
Sorry.
Okay, one more time from the beginning.
Sakura?
Is your body okay?
I might be artificially created,
but I'm a Variant, too.
I'm completely fine.
That's good.
Karen's really looking
forward to your concert.
Looking forward to, huh...
Sakura?
Everyone says they like my songs.
That Kirishima Sakura's songs
reach deep into their hearts.
But that really isn't the case.
The reason why my songs affect everyone
is because I'm not your normal singer.
It's because I'm a Variant.
What do you mean?
Currently, a large number of humans
are infected with the Variant virus,
and that's what I tap into,
since I'm a Variant.
That's why I can touch their hearts.
That's why they say they like my songs.
My singing is nothing but deception.
Sakura...
My songs aren't reaching anyone.
My actual singing isn't...
I don't think that's true.
Your songs have something about them.
So the virus has nothing to do with it.
You saw it too, didn't you, Hayato-kun?
That Savage reacted to my voice!
That was because of the virus, too...
Back then...
Back then, I thought
your song was really good.
I don't know much about music,
but your singing makes me feel better.
Your song reached deep into the hearts
of both Karen and me.
That was before you became a Variant, right?
Yeah...
It's okay.
Your voice is reaching everyone fine.
Hayato-kun, thank you.
I think I'm going to fall
even deeper in love with you.
I'm going to do my best
during tomorrow's concert.
Yeah. I'm looking forward to it.
Hundred On!
Here I go, everyone!
Have fun today!
This is great! Sakura-san's so cool!
Yeah.
I'm going to sing this song
in front of all of you for the first time.
It's a precious song to me.
This is...
Do you remember?
Could that girl from back then be....
...Sakura-san?
Her song is reaching...
...everyone's hearts.
It really is.
I still can't believe it.
I didn't know that Sakura-san
was the girl we met.
I feel the same way.
That night I met the two of you,
I realized just how fun singing could be.
Thanks to that, I became a singer.
It's been a while. Thank you, Karen-chan.
S-Same here!
Let's sing together next time we meet.
Like we did before.
S-Sure!
Charlotte, about Sakura's voice...
Leave it to me.
I'll look into it, I promise.
I owe you that much.
Hayato-kun, we were only together
for a short time, but thank you.
Yeah.
S-S-Sakura-san is
k-kissing Nii-san?!
I'll definitely come and
see you again, Hayato-kun!
Really soon!
Hayato-kun... Hayato-kun.
Heavy...
Huh?
S-Sorry!
Sakura? Why...?
I told you I'd come to see you really soon.
Kirishima Sakura!
I'm going to detain you
on the charge of illegal trespassing.
Hayato-kun, I'm scared!
Good morning!
Why are the president and Kirishima-san here?!
You two are in the way, so leave.
Right, Hayato-kun?
"Hayato-kun," my foot!
Get away from Kisaragi Hayato!
Hey, this is the men's dorm.
Girls can't come in here!
That's why the president and this girl
need to leave right now!
I'm amazed you have the gall to say that!
You need to remember your position here!
W-Wait!
I do!
Get out, all of you!
No!
The Captured Wild Rose Princess